{"question":"6ч + 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 20мин + 50мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 50мин + 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 50мин + 25мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 50мин + 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч + 50мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 30мин + 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 50мин + 50мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 55мин + 35мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 25мин + 30мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 45мин + 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 5мин + 40мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 55мин + 1ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 20мин + 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 20мин + 50мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 45мин + 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 30мин + 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 20мин + 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 55мин + 15мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 10мин + 50мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 15мин + 40мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч + 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 55мин + 50мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 5мин + 30мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 20мин + 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 30мин + 35мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 15мин + 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 30мин + 50мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 5мин + 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 40мин + 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 30мин + 1ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 45мин + 40мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 45мин + 15мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч + 35мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 5мин + 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 15мин + 40мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 25мин + 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 30мин + 40мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 5мин + 35мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 30мин + 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 10мин + 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 5мин + 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 15мин + 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 5мин + 30мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 40мин + 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч + 15мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 55мин + 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч + 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 55мин + 15мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 30мин + 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 40мин + 15мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 15мин + 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 15мин + 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 20мин + 25мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 50мин + 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 25мин + 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч + 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 25мин + 35мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 5мин + 1ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 55мин + 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 20мин + 30мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 5мин + 50мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 40мин + 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 45мин + 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 25мин + 30мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 25мин + 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 15мин + 25мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 15мин + 30мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 20мин + 35мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 15мин + 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 15мин + 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 5мин + 30мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 50мин + 15мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 25мин + 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 35мин + 40мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 25мин + 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 45мин + 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч + 1ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 50мин + 25мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 30мин + 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 20мин + 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 20мин + 1ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 50мин + 40мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 20мин + 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 50мин + 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 40мин + 30мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 55мин + 35мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 5мин + 1ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 25мин + 25мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 45мин + 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 15мин + 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 20мин + 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 40мин + 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 5мин + 15мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 45мин + 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 50мин + 15мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 30мин + 50мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 35мин + 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 5мин + 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 35мин + 30мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
